{
    "subject": "resource/Kingdom_of_Burundi",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Burundian_franc",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Kingdom of Burundi is Burundian franc.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9773658514022827,
            "question": "Is the Burundian franc the official currency of Burundi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.888949453830719,
            "question": "What is the currency of the Kingdom of Burundi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7820106148719788,
            "question": "What other currencies are commonly used in Burundi besides the Burundian franc?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7319982051849365,
            "question": "Where can you exchange foreign currency for Burundian francs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6717886924743652,
            "question": "What is the name of the Burundian franc?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5584419369697571,
            "question": "Has the value of the Burundian franc fluctuated over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5560766458511353,
            "question": "How is the value of the Burundian franc determined?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5252504348754883,
            "question": "Can you buy goods and services in Burundi using Burundian francs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3971007168292999,
            "question": "What are some challenges facing the Burundian franc?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3418658971786499,
            "question": "What factors influence the exchange rate of the Burundian franc?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Kingdom of Burundi is Burundian franc.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9131_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some challenges facing the Burundian franc?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9131_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you buy goods and services in Burundi using Burundian francs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9131_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the value of the Burundian franc determined?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9131_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9131_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9131_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9131_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9131_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9131_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9131_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9131_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9131_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9131_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9131_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents confirms that the official currency of Burundi is the Burundian Franc, which supports the statement that \"The currency of Kingdom of Burundi is Burundian franc.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}